Iyris P. Vigil

604 -704 -2632

iyrisvigil@gmail.com

in /iyris

/iyriss

SUMMARY

A full stack web developer with a background in graphic design and marketing, I've always liked the idea behind bringing life to static designs. My approach to coding centers around a smooth user experience and I enjoy the process of moving from design to implementation.

PROJECTS

Easy Ride

Working project for the Victoria Therapeutic Riding Association to manage users, horses, and bookings for rides, events, and lessons.
(React. Rails. Axios.

(React, Rails, Axios, Material UI, PostgreSQL)

Interview Scheduler

A single page web app that the user can create, edit and delete interview appointments (React, HTML, CSS,Axios, PostgreSQL, Jest, Cypress, Storybook)

Tweeter

Single-page responsive Twitter clone (HTML, CSS, Javascript, AJAX, Node, Express)

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Javascript, HTML, CSS, SASS, Ruby, SQL.

Frameworks, Libraries and Environments: Node.js, React, Rails, Ajax,

Express, EJS, JQuery, Bootstrap, Material UI.

Systems, CMS and Databases: Git, PostgreSQL, Wordpress.

Testing: Cypress, Mocha/Chai, Storybook, Jest.

Adobe Creative Cloud: Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign, XD, After Effects,

Premiere Pro.

Spoken Languages: English, German, Spanish.

EXPERIENCE

Education Coach and Marketing Assistant *Next Goal Agency*

Vancouver, BC

Oct 2019 – April 2020

- Created engaging image and video content for social media accounts and website.
- Helped managing website content for SEO.
- Communicated with potential immigration and education clients.

Digital Marketing Assistant Smart Web Canada

Vancouver, BC

Sept 2018 - May 2019

- Optimized client websites for search engines through analysis content, keywords and Title and Meta tags.
- Introduced social media scheduling.
- Wrote and maintained social media posts calendar for clients on a weekly basis.
- Created content for email marketing campaigns with Mailchimp

Sales and Marketing Intern

Gran Canaria, Spain

July 2015 – October 2015

- Seaside Hotels, S.L.
- Processed weekly sales reports, board and sales preview statistics.
- Organised marketing plans to develop strategies and processed office correspondence in English, German and Spanish.
- Database maintenance and merchandise inventory management.

EDUCATION

Lighthouse Labs

Aug 2020 - Nov 2020

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Vancouver, BC

Vancouver, BC

Vancouver, BC

British Columbia Institute of Technology

Media Techniques and Marketing Comms Certificate

Jan 2018 - June 2019

SELC Career College

Business Foundations and Communications

Jan 2017 - Dec 2017

University of Applied Sciences Salzburg

Oct 2013 - Nov 2016

B.A. in Business Innovation and Management

Salzburg, Austria